gcitrading.com 2015-06-12

# Privacy Policy - GCI Financial

GCI Financial LLC ("GCI")  respects each individual's right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. The provisions of this notice apply to former clients, current clients, and applicants.

### Personal Information

When you apply for or maintain a demo or live account with GCI, we collect personal information you provided  for business purposes,  informing you about promotions, products and services that may be of interest to you, and providing customer service.

### About Cookies

Cookies are small files containing information that a Web site uses to track its visitors. GCI may set and access GCI cookies on your computer, enabling us to learn which advertisements and promotions bring users to our Web site. GCI or any of its divisions may use cookies in connection with GCI's products and services to track your activities on our Web sites. Such information that we collect and share would be anonymous and not personally identifiable.

### Security Technology

GCI uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology in order to protect certain information that you submit. This type of technology protects you from having your information intercepted by anyone other than GCI while it is being transmitted to us. We work hard to ensure that our Web sites are secure and that they meet industry standards. We also use other safeguards such as firewalls, authentication systems (e.g., passwords and personal identification numbers), and access control mechanisms to control unauthorized access to systems and data.

### Sharing Information with Third Parties

GCI does not disclose, share or sell your personal information to any third party.       

### Legal Disclosure           

Under limited circumstances, GCI may disclose your personal information to third parties as permitted by, or to comply with, applicable laws and regulations. For example, we may disclose personal information to cooperate with regulatory authorities and law enforcement agencies to comply with subpoenas or other official requests, and as necessary to protect our rights or property. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not use your personal information for any other purpose, unless we describe how such information will be used at the time you disclose it to us or we obtain your permission.

### Opt Out       

Your personal information is automatically deleted from the demo trading platforms after 30 days.

If you wish to stop receiving any emails from GCI after that period, you can use the opt out link provided at the bottom of all of our email communications or contact [compliance@gcitrading.com](mailto:compliance@gcitrading.com) and request your opt out, in which case GCI will permanently delete your personal information in our database.

### Changes to this privacy statement 

In the event GCI materially changes this Privacy Statement, the revised Privacy  Statement will promptly be posted to the Web sites and we will post a notice on  our Web sites informing you of such changes. You agree to accept posting of a  revised Privacy Statement electronically on the Web site as actual notice to  you. Any dispute over our Privacy Statement is subject to this notice and the  GCI Customer Agreement. If you have any questions that this statement does not  address, please contact a GCI representative.

You may contact GCI for any reason under this Privacy Policy, or otherwise, as  follows:

GCI Financial LLC

Mitchell House

P.O.Box 174 The Valley

Anguilla, British West Indies

email:  [info@gcitrading.com](mailto:info@gcitrading.com)

telephone:  \+ 1 800 604 2457
